[Music]
In the name of God, I greet you and have a good time.
Dear friends and companions, we are very happy to be with
you with the new Trident Course of the Zeus Group. This course is published in its entirety in
a dedicated playlist with the same name on the
official Zeus YouTube page at the address Zeus Forex Channel,
and all sessions can be viewed in order from the
first part.  In this course,
you will see 9 one-hour teaching sessions
presented conceptually and practically.  After
watching each session, you can practice
and then watch 6 short half-hour sessions of
troubleshooting by friends who participated in the course
and gain a better understanding of the material.
After that, you will enter the next teaching session.
To communicate directly with us and use the
bug plans, simply send a message to the Telegram ID of the
Aderline Admin group and stay in touch with us
.
Success in your trading career, my
dears.
[Music]
In the name of God, session of
trading course d.
This session is about Kings and their types, and
now the position of these Kings.
Well, in sessions
one and two, we talked about many things in detail,
but in this session, we will start
with the most important principle that we see in the chart,
and with it, we will hit you all over the head throughout the day with those that are
possible, called Kings or
Nodes in some sets
.  So first, let
me give an explanation about these knots, or rather, these
kings.  Well, on the chart, it is usually seen
that in many places, in many places in the market, we
expect a series of areas that have a drop-
base rally or vice versa, a rally-base drop.
For example, if you look at all the charts,
there is a kink that consists of a few bearish candles,
let me color this differently, a few
bearish candles, then a bullish candle, and again a
bearish candle, which I identify as a king knot.
This symbol. Well, first, let's learn how to draw
this correctly together. So, what
should we pay attention to on our chart now, and
what is the position of these kings, and what position and what
name should we give them? We will go through these together one by one.
First, for example, the
most basic
topic that many friends have in previous discussions was
that we have a low or an SNR,
a support system that has been broken, and the
breakdown that is now forming in that area is
called king learning. For example, if you have a low
here and the price crosses it and
again  It goes back on this line
and comes back down again.  That means he crosses this line 3 times
.  Look, now you
assume this is the low, the price breaks here,
comes back, and
crosses this line again.
So this is the correct way to draw our king.
That is, from where the price has returned to the
area given by the retracement, and again it
must
be broken again in this lower king low,
that is, this low must be confirmed again. So they
say that the confirmation of the king price must be from this low
that I show you with a circle.
Now you can see on the chart that if this is
identified as a one, this price area has returned
once, the black line has returned below it.
Now yes, we will discuss the topics ahead about
these areas becoming major or the term being large,
but first let's learn
what we want to draw on the chart. So here is the
correct way to draw from the
area that returns to the most extreme
area that the retracement gives, and then this
low that has returned inside must be broken again and the top is the
beginning and end of the box that we draw
.  Now, in my graphic, I've drawn several models of
this situation for you here.
For example, see if there is a D to SNR or a H.
Here, the price broke this
area and a few candles later, the
price returned to this area and reconfirmed it
.  That confirmation should be on the upper edge here
because our kink
is bullish, meaning it was
created on the broken bars. The price should
reject this upper area again for us to
say that our kink is confirmed
here. Let's say it's confirmed on this area. Well,
in the future, I'll tell you
when we can draw this king. This means
this king is the
first and last one. This means that this king
is established for us because there is a discussion about
when this king will no longer grow. We'll get to that for now.
The same initial discussion, which is the
correct way to draw this, is in the
schematic that I drew next to it. The ones that are
broken, the price passes through it, returns,
and here it is confirmed in this green circle.
Now, this is an example of a
downtrend. Here, in the second one, you see this was
one, here are two examples of a downtrend where the price
came to the line, broke the line, retraced, and came back to the
lower area, which is confirmed again. In this breakdown, the
lower edge area is our kink confirmation.
Well, this is a type that forms in the breakdowns of the lows and the
SNR lines.  We
have a number of different types of kings in the chart.
We first consider the position of these types,
then we put them in order, for example
.  Some kings are
formed on the breakdown area, like this number 1 and 2. An
example of an upward trend and a downward trend means a breakdown
on the same line or high. If you draw a line
or SNA, this is not a king breakdown
on the breakdown area. But on the chart,
we have kings that form before the breakdown area,
like the number 1, which has a high.
The price came before these highs, made a king,
and when these highs were broken and the price that
returned here was not given to it. Well, these must
be separated. First, let's learn to know what it
does and what expectations we have from this cake. We will get
to it gradually. You can see that there is a
downward trend here. The price of this low
broke from it. When it broke here, it
did not form the breakdown area, but before it
broke this area, it formed one. Or,
some of the
links that
we see in the chart are after these highs.
That is, the third example, and the fourth example here
is a high. When the price
crosses these highs, it kinks higher.  From these
levels, it gives back. Now, in some cases, when we get
to holding,
you will see that hold is done on these areas.
So now, our kings are divided
in this way: a king in the
broken areas is one before our areas, that is, before the high, before the high,
before the snr.
Some kings are also broken with a distance from these
highs, and now the price before it makes a king.
Let's look at a few examples of these on the
chart together. Some examples that
exist, for example, here in the U. Now, I have
taken many names from the chart, but for the
sake of examples, here is a
lemon with a D to L here
.  Well, after the price
broke this area, meaning the price came here,
broke here, if you look, it
returned to the broken area a bit and
continued its way again and was confirmed in this area as well. That
is, we will now tell our kink where it was confirmed.
When it is confirmed here,
it has created a beginning and an end for us that we can
specify. Just for now, I do
n't want to do this in a crude way, meaning that
some of these kings may, for example,
cross this line once, go lower,
confirm, and cross again. Yes, this
is also a type, but for now, let's know what we want first.
Then we will talk about
when and when we should draw this box
and say, this can't be bigger than this box anymore.
That is, it can't be bigger than this box
anymore. It doesn't create an ek, but it ca
n't be bulky. We will discuss it in the next discussions of the
opposite areas. When the price
reaches these opposite areas, we say that this king code that
becomes bulky becomes stable because it has
reached the opposite area. This is one of our examples.  That was
our first example. Now let's move on to the
next example. Here are the
examples of the
three and four highs, the
same as the J schematic. Here are the numbers H and 4
that we drew here. This is an example
before the break of these highs and after the break of these highs.
These are the things that happened before and after the break. Well,
friends who have studied RTM now know
that some of these areas are known as
rally-base rally.
These
areas are usually formed before now and then they are broken
.
Now here is King number 5 before the defeat and
King number 4 after the defeat.  Identifying these are
a series of areas that I will call in the future the
F levels or areas of thought that create our effusions
.  These words are related to Darsamuna.
This is for our acquaintance.  So first it broke and then it
broke.
So now the second example.
Well, here's an example where there's a leak. A
leak has come out before and
done something wrong.  Now, this is the topic of Hold'em that we're
talking about today.  This is before the broken one,
meaning the example created before these
.
After the failure is done, well, this is
the number of the example before this, Lu Kinking before
Lue, and after the failure, now it's back to it.
These numbers that we see here are related to
this inside our schematic, which I wrote 1 2 3 4 5 6 7
here, this inside V, inside our images,
which I wrote this 6 now, this is related to example
number.  So here is example number four, where
a king was formed after this low and the price was
now
unable to
cross the broken area once
and return.  This is King after our defeat.
Let's go to number 4. Here we have a high again.
Now the price has come before and after this
area that was broken. It created a level and
returned to it in the future.
This is number 4 again. Here you see a low. It has
broken both before this area and has a
king, which is here,
and after this area.
We need to know whether this kink is before or
after the broken area.
So
now the next exercise is
this is a type of number 8 and now
some examples here is an example of
number 4 kink before this low low
that we have here and the king before the break that is
on the right now that king did not form and
came back in the future let's
go to this area this is another example of kink before the
break
here low and this is the kink that before this this is
the type of number hand
from low broken and this itself can be for example as a
kink that after this low now we have to
look to the left but what is currently in
our picture is the breakdown of this low that
created a zone after this and
created a level and kept the price low and
reached this area again now it can use this
as an
area that has liquidity behind it
and make a decline so let's go to the next example
well here is also an example of number four where the kink
before breaking
like the previous one
the price comes before the low a zone
makes a kink a turn and then breaks this
which now in the future the price comes to it  It rises
and falls.  So let's go to the schematic where we can
examine our original and other examples together.  So we have learned so far
that we have four types of kings. Now this
example is not a chart.
We have three types of kings. Kinkro, the area of ​​the break before the
break and after the break. Well, these kings can now be,
apart from the high and low breaks, they
can be of the same type, meaning that a king
can be formed from one that is similar to
itself. In the term of noun, the word sep king is
used. For example, if we look at number 5,
these highs have been broken. The blue kink has
formed. It has become unlikely. That is, here it has become unlikely.
The price of a high has risen again. It has come back
below the king. It has fallen back and here it has been confirmed.
When it is confirmed here, it means that this
king that we have to draw, so to speak, is the soup.
This becomes the final soup. Now this is an
upward example. This is a downward example.
This is the red box that the father broke.
And this can be these examples before and
after. Like the three types above, we can
also draw the swap from this king.
This is a downward example. And you look at the
number.
The link that was formed before the high,
that is, as  Before the re-break, the
swap was confirmed here and we draw this
result, so to speak,
in the
RT I call them the swap key. Now, examples on the
chart, for example, I want to show you now that
we have a
bar here, you have a one-way bar here, so
this is
our bullish king,
and here this king is the result of the pink break, the confrontation
between here and the
lowest low that has passed through this area,
maybe this low, for example, comes back from here,
we, whatever this amount of penetration that has
happened on this lower line of our blue kink,
that is, maybe the price has come here now or it
may hit this with a pipette
or penetrates more, we, from the
lowest
if it was here, well, our low here, it will be the
end of our retracement here, and this must
be confirmed. If not, it had more penetration, well, it will be
more penetration than this until the end of the regress. We wait until
this low breaks again,
here is a top to the bottom of the inkingo, we will box the top to the bottom of
this low, this low high, we will draw a box, so
this is how it will be, for example, the correct way to
draw our king, so now
We learned that a
broken king can
give us a soup king here.
Well, these are some examples that I showed you
in my schematic. Now, let's go and see
the examples in
those
charts. So, let's complete this.
Well, we've come this far that after the soup,
this king is useful to us. We can
use them as a range. Now, in numbers
7 and 8, we have to come to our discussion. Let's
talk about these examples of the ginkar. But before we
go to them, first, we have to come to. Now, we
realized that the position of the kings themselves can be
on the high before the high and after the high. So, there are
some details, more details, that the kings
have that we should examine. What does a king
in the lower tier have that we want to
kill it?  Now, in this image you are
looking at, there are some that are
broken.  A beginning and end of the blue box,
as a key, formed on the red line, that is,
as a SNR or something in this key,
and the price has risen again.  So
I came up with this as a lower time frame or
I drew the components inside this blue king box.
What components are inside a
king?  So when we
break a SNR or a HIU, well,
at the time of the retrace, that is, from the top down, it
forms an origin at the top, and when
the end of the retrace is completed and it
starts moving upwards, an
origin moves again for the end of the
retrace path upwards again.
Now, we will work together on how to get this origin
in the next discussions, but you
should know what components are here.
One of the components is known as the origin.
This blue box and my red box are the
start of the movement. The
start of the movement. And one of the other components is that the
sides of the
nine that are broken from the left, Mr. Minori,
who is now called Ares for these
blue boxes or as the opening in
previous discussions, this green box
was known as the swimming opening, but I do
n't want to talk about the words opening and
origin here, and I don't know if it's a warf, l,
m, l, and all of them.  They
are identified as kings by the choices.
We only know that these are a series of kings.
Why do we want to kill them?
So, based on the inkings' violations, we can
identify a path that now shapes the
charts for us based on the stories that are worth it
.  That is,
we learn a series of prices by reading the chart based on the
chart pattern, and there are a series of footprints or a
series of patterns that contain these movements,
and the market is looking for these movements.
Now this is the opening of this green box, the
red box is the origin up and the blue box is the origin
down. We came in the D period, this origin that
is up and because the failure was happening on the side where it was, we
identified it as EL. We said
this is the log level, which many people came and
said, "What else did you make?" And from
these discussions, this was
a simplification
[of music]
for a better understanding of the topic. We did
not invent anything ourselves. All these discussions that
exist are now.
Now someone has mentioned these, then my help has been
cooked and turned over by hand. Now
this difference in the type of angle of views
can now, for example, increase or decrease. There is nothing.
Now you say QM. Now
QM. Maybe at one time it was said
as an additional word, but my help saw
that it was on the chart. Now we
considered it as A. The same philosophy
was in the ship. We did not want to add anything,
nor cause confusion to anyone. Now, for example,
you do not need to add this at all. I do
not name Kinko at all anymore.  I call it King
or Order as A or A or I do
n't know, I don't look at anything. I say Order
here, there is an order in this area,
there is an order, but this identification of these
components helps us because if the price of
one of these components forms a breach, for
example, if our red box is here
and in the future, by a negative price in the future, it hits
this area, so to speak, it hits this, so to speak, it hits
this,
so to speak, it creates a perspective or a trading philosophy
for me that why it hit
this final and didn't reach my blue area is
the reason that when we enter the kinkum, we
examine these more fractally
to optimize our entry areas.
No, now I'm confused. Yes, all of these are basically the same
kinkum, which you now know as a
rally base drop
or anything or a base. Now you can say in the
high time a rally base drop or a drop
base rally. It doesn't matter. You can do
whatever you like, just without us for what?  We want to
use these, so the components
that are inside a king, one
as the origin
after the failures and one at the time of the origin
when the end of the retrace is determined, now
moves up, so that from one gensen, that is,
both of these kings, this king and this king, both of them are
obtained from the same gensen and both of them are of the same type,
now there is not much difference, considering
the amount of retrace and failures that are on my left, it
helps us to obtain me.
This is the same simple kink that was in number
one, but it's a one-way break and is identified as an
opening.  So these are the components of
our kink as the opening now and the two origins
that exist above and below.
[Music]
Now let's
look at a few examples of these kings. Let's
find an example on the chart and let's drag it a
little bit higher.  So, for
example, if we cut from here in this chart, we would
consider this as a king.  So now, I want to give you an example of the kink that
exists here, a sample of King
Swab to Swab.
We have a king here
[music]
here is a king,
now this king itself is the result of a king from the left and
in a king time frame below now sitting,
for example here
where both of these kings are the first king
before the broken hi, let me show you a little bit more to the left
.
So, if we have a failure here, is
there a failure or a kink here
or can we pull the failure?  The bottom king is the
top edge line before breaking.
This is the king before the top edge.   The
top that was formed here once
and the next time it was one higher
hit it again. This is that we will erase the first one
but draw the last one.
Now I will use green color to
separate it from this blue one.
This is as a king. As you
can see, this is a low. If you want to
show a low here, you can do
this as a low. Then in front of it
on the right side, what broke this low or the end of
our green box?
Well, there is another king opposite, this
area is before the break,
this king is before the break, this green low and the
kink that broke on the green low is here.
This is the area of ​​this low after crossing the
green low, the blue low, and returning to the area and
confirming again, that is, look at this confirmation. Here, it
was confirmed.
See, the lower low of
our pink box price was confirmed and in the return, the price
came back and hit the back of our pink area
and made a king swap again. You can
see this from above, from its highest
to the lowest area that the rates gave and
confirmed here.  Look, it's confirmed here.
When the inking was confirmed here, it
hit the blue upper edge line.  Now
we want to look at this blue box and
identify its components.  See what components are inside.
According to the same schematic we had here,
we said here are a series of components: one
has a top origin, one has a bottom origin, one has an
opening. Let's draw this in this structure we have,
one by one. So here we need to.
Now I'm going to delete this annotation.
In order to get to this concept, I
drew these one after the other so that we can understand what we want to do in
this blue box. But
to get those areas, now
we need this to be, for example, the bottom edge or
this kink itself.  I'll come clean this up, I'll come kill
this scum that was made from soup
.
Look, this is Kingamon with the color Aran
King. We don't have more than three colors.  A
red king.  We have a red box
here.  We have a red box.
We have a blue box
and we also have a box that now has areas that are
carpeted, that have not been touched, that have not been tested, that
we do not use these three colors anymore.
In our drawing box, the
red box is drawn here, and I have to
draw a blue box opposite it, from this area up to
this area. So let's go see if there are any components
inside it, so I can show you those components
.  Now I'll move the time frame
down a bit.  I'll delete these two extra boxes
to show that
these two boxes are for us.  I'll
lower the timer.  So
now I'm going to move the 5-minute time frame up a bit
.  I'll make this cake too.
So this blue kink is the result of the failure of the red kink
.  So if we look at it this way,
in this kink, this blue kink that I drew the highest and
lowest, we want to find the
upper origin and the lower virgin
.  Well, all kings, for example, have some
differences in drawing these.  But
we're going to
use a single framework, one topic at a time,
so that in the future, when all our friends
look at other friends' charts, they can understand
how I got this king.
Now, for example, in this area, you saw that I
came from an hour ago, 5 minutes ago. You can
also go in a minute. But here, if we
go in a minute, the fractal amount is higher, meaning that the
number of
these seven and eight that are here may
be more. Now, I am using a simple 5-
minute chart so that I can see this fractal less on the
chart. Now, this kink is
red. Our kink is red in the 5-minute time frame.
If you look, it broke here at first,
meaning it broke here
and the price retraced here.
And if I show this in yellow, the
difference with that box means that the
price came here, crossed the end of the red box,
then came down, and again it was confirmed here,
and went one higher and reached. Look closely. It
reached a king before breaking.
If we consider this low as an
area, there is a king before breaking
this low. Or left to left, meaning, if you
want to look again, left to left, I will make this
big peak sooner. Now, for example, I
want to draw these lows one by one.
Our line now.  I'm drawing with annotations that
you need to know this low is broken, this clinic
is in mid
again, this should be red,
this is before the reset, here the samp gives you, yes,
what happens here, well, come back again,
for our blue box, we need to look at a red box here,
so what did this red box do? It broke, the
price on this low was broken, a king was made, the
price went down, the price went back into this king,
this
price again, this king held the price and
made a lower low. Between here, the word for holding is holding, holding, holding,
holding the price
by a king. They say holding
now, a kink that existed here and was the
result of breaking this low.  When it
has returned from this low below
and the hold has been done here, it has
succeeded in recording a low, that is,
sending the price from this low to the base area to
hit a lower low. This is called holding.
Now, it is a very difficult thing to deal with.
This is holding, but it has a
very simple definition. Holding the price by
a low. Now, the question arises, where is this king
holding? We must first explain the details,
then we must understand what is
important for us to achieve this.
For example, from now on, I will say that the base may be at some point in the
middle because we need to identify the order.
It is not to keep, to keep, to keep, to keep, to keep, to keep,
not to keep the pattern.
We read based on our reading, we look at a series of
evidence, and based on that, we make a
decision. This is what I said.
Then the price held, broke, broke again, and came
across a kink that broke above this
low. This is what happens. Now, another low, I will
come, a low lower. There is a
space
between this hold and this area.  Yes.
Look, there is a space here.  There is a space
between these two where the price has now
come here,
returned to the upper area and reacted again, and
this space has caused something to happen.  It caused
the price to react again and
fall a bit lower.  Now I'm going to clean this up.   We
want to write, let's go back to
drawing the details of our blue box.
So our red box broke here. When
this broke, you went away. Now, there is an
expectation that this
yellow box is the result of the failure of
this
[music]
kink. Our red box here once
held the price. Now, the expectation is that it will hold the price
.
When the price comes from above, it is knocked down here,
comes back up and comes back up, it is confirmed,
meaning the soup itself
gives us this one, from this low to this
high.   So
this is the kink, meaning this front kink that
is identified as an origin, the origin of the
retrace move, meaning this king wants to retrace
and then come back until it is confirmed from this line
above it, so this king is the origin
above. This is how it happens here, you often see
that the areas change.
Now this is the simplest case.  Sometimes
you see, well, this King doesn't exist.
There is a left now.  We'll help you achieve this
.  But now we
have this red kink using soups, which is the
result of Origin's failure against the
price.  So after it's approved,
when do we draw this red box?
Where is this red box compared to when it is confirmed
?  When it crosses the low, that is, here it is
exactly confirmed, see
here it is confirmed, then it comes and writes itself
to the opposite area. Well, this opposite area, as you can see, was
an
origin of the move, that is, as you
saw in the schematic.
First, let me explain this in the schematic.
Similarly, this low that you saw
broke a king low, meaning the kink before breaking the
lower low, and the kink that turned over,
we considered this as a sub or origin of the move.
In this schematic, I tell you that this is the
simplest type of pull. So, here, if
our low is this, this king brought the price down, we
have this king in front of it, so this is the
origin of the previous move, meaning here, this
drop,
base, rally, drop,
base, that is, the drop of
a base
and the rally back
here.
Now I will delete this,
so this is the
origin of the move. Now, we want to
find the origin of this end of the retracement.  Well,
look at how to find this.  We did
n't have an area like above to get soup from
.  But if we look at when
the price came and entered our red box,
this low is the lowest low that was
created here. A king was formed in line with the breakdown of this
edge here,
and the price first formed the opposite after clearing the lower area.
What created this low?  This king in
the return of the king is opposite or opposite as the
origin of the movement. Well, this type of pulling is
not always like this. You often see that, for example, your
origin or area is a little lower than the
top. I say that we should consider this as a twenty-two task
to help us get to the content
ahead and make them
better for us. So here is the
beginning of
this golf. This was the beginning of our breach. Here is the breach of the
opposite box. In the return, this was the origin of the fall.
This last kink that brought the price and created the last low. In the
return, this same origin breaks this last kink and creates the kink method at the top. The origin of this movement is not always like this. Here it was like this and the movement upwards and the confirmation of the blue box. When it crosses these, our box is
confirmed and that opening is the result of the re-breaking of
these. That is, now we have that opening that
was in our schematic and was green and here it is also
green. This is this opening here, for
example, as a one-opening opening
for the blue box that is very similar to this
maneuver.  We don't think we are working more with this original line, we
are working with this red line, and we are drawing this
yellow line and the lower area, for example, the opening.
Now we are thinking, "Help me," these things
enter our minds, and we
no longer want to draw boxes in the square. These boxes do
not trade alone. The person himself does the trading
based on the diagnosis he makes on the chart.
So now you understand how to get this
.  You understand how one holds
.  For example, we consider this king
as a failure when it
is confirmed and consider the FTB made to this king
as a hold
.  If there is an order inside the ink,
the price should come to that area
and hit the low again.
After it hit the low, we call it the
kink that held. Now, in one of the
masters in the academy, for example,
one of the conditions for holding the limit blog was
considered, but now he has
not given a complete explanation with him. How far should the hold go? Should it hit the low
or hold to the origin of another
area? Now we have to go through it.
We will just go through it. Now
I said that, for example, one of the views is this, but
what we see on the chart is that
in my opinion, what is on the chart
should be this kink that is holding here,
definitely hit a low lower. Well, this is one of the
components of our kink. So, the upper area is the origin of the fall.
This is an origin here and
this is an origin of the rise. Now later, you wanted to call this
what you wanted to call it. I don't know, call this the tree,
call this the bottom one, just without saying that
here.  With this, the price has started to go up, the
word is involved, and these are not the things that are
important to us on the chart, how to use
these areas,
and remember, the price must definitely
confirm here, and this is the price that we are
talking about here as a gap. We are dealing with it. I
am not saying that we are not dealing with it. At one time, we were
dealing with it, but it is not very difficult. I mean, it
must come from this area. Sometimes, many of
my friends had seen in the discussions that
this had a deep retracement, they would
come here and take this whole thing as a gap.
For example, they would take this gap here, it has
opened too much, it has a lot of it. It
needs surgery. If you want to do
something about this,
we will not consider this as a gap anymore.
So let's summarize these things
that we said, and now let's do some exercises.
God willing, the rest of my discussions will be for the next session.
So let's summarize that first we learned
how to draw a Kinko correctly, how to
draw a Kinko, then we came to ascending kings,
like the schematic of a  Descending kings schematic 2 and
types of kings, meaning in terms of positions, I
mean in terms of positions, the position before the breakdown of a
high-level or a king after its breakdown, which could be
number 4 after it, and some kings are
now or the result of a king breakdown,
like this, for example, these are broken, a king is
created, then they are red, swap, this is it. So,
in terms of the
position of the king, we have broken three types of positions before and
after, now I have a model that is itself the result of
its own type, which may be, for example, whether it is before,
like this number 6 or like number 5, it
forms an area.
Take the trouble to practice each of these types of kings in your
journal. First draw the schematic, and make
examples of them.
Then we came to A. Now we talked about the components of the king.
What are the details of the king? We came to D. We came to D.
In addition to the upper area, the lower area and its opening, we
also drew examples of these on the chart. We
talked about holding. Now we talked about holding and we
talked about it one by one. This will be the
next session, now only you will have these types of
kings with  Take care of these details for the
next session for training. Then our
next session will be about holding.
Holding on the broken. Building
before the broken. And then we will come to these kings
based on the place. For example, now we will put the position
where they found the Ace.
Now our next session will be
on the one and the one above that you all know
as the left.
Kings that are formed before the compression
and the king that is used as the ace. We
will come to all of these one by one or these holds
that are formed before the broken and after the broken. And the
examples that we tried to
talk about here now. You saw a few examples here.
Now if there is another one, for
example, this is a
kink that has now held, an example of
one, that is, this low has broken, the
low has broken, the kink that was made
here has been confirmed, this is as an opening
itself and the price has come to hold, this hold is
lower than the low that came. This can be a low that has come to
a low.
That is, the blue box hold box caused
a low to be created. This is one of its examples.
And the next example, for example, here is an example of its own
kind. These are their own kind.
Consider this. It was broken by the blue box. The
red box came. The swap on the blue box
is called a kink swap. And an example. Now,
try to get these examples in your journal.
For example, this number was broken before the low.
And for example, here is
example number 5. These were broken by the
higher blue box and confirmed again
by the red box. The blue box is in the grid.
The price now knows based on it, the
position and the time. Do you hold or not? Here we go.
These are exercises. Try to put them
in your journal during the week. I wish
you all a good day. I
hope this video is useful for you too.
Bye. Hey
[Music]
Hey